homedesignlover.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Home Design Lover

Here at homedesignlover.com, We respect your privacy like how we respect the website. One of our duty is to protect your personal information that you may provide us using our website.

### DISCLOSURE & DISCLAIMERS

All information provided by Homedesignlover.com is all correct as of time of writing and is intended for general informational purposes. 

All photos on the blog are not the property of Homedesignlover.com. Rather, passionate writers feature amazing home design ideas to inspire our readers in building their homes. Nevertheless, we acknowledge proper crediting to our source through indicating the source URL on the images that we have used in our posts. 

No content including photos can be reproduced without the express written permission of Homedesignlover.com and its writers.

### PRIVACY & GDPR COMPLIANCE

Homedesignlover.com is GDPR Compliant. 

GDPR Policy requires the following so that you – our readers- have the right to a) be informed regarding how the data is collected and used b) have access to the data about you c) ask to change the data about you d) ask to delete the data about you e) ask Homedesignlover.com to stop sending your newsletters 

**Usage Tracking**

Homedesignlover.com’s web server automatically collects information such as domain type, browser used, and IP address once it is used or viewed. 

This information, however, are utilised for statistical purposes only and will be used to improve our site’s content. The team fully respect the individual privacy of our viewers and users, therefore any information gathered will not be sold to other organisations. 

**Cookies**

A text file called “cookie” is placed in the browser files of your computer once Homedesignlover.com is viewed or used. 

It does not, however, contain personal information except for the data you have personally supplied. It only allow us to relate the use of the site to any information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. 

Homedesignlover.com uses cookies to track user traffic patterns while our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates. 

We would remind everyone that third parties ad server companies may also place and read cookies in your browser, or use web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on Homedesignlover.com. 

Cookies may be refused by turning them off in your browser. If you’ve set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. 

Cookies need not to be turned on to use this site. 

**E-Mail Subscription**

Subscribing to the Homedesignlover.com’s newsletter means you will receive the newsletter as and when it is sent. 

If you wish to unsubscribe from this service, you can do so at any time either using the link in the newsletter emails or by contacting Homedesignlover directly. Once removed, you will not be re-added to the mailing list, nor will your data be stored or sold. 

Additionally, if you are an EU resident and wish to have your comments taken down, please get in touch with Homedesignlover and they will be permanently deleted. We do not retain secondary copies of our readers personal information or sell any of those data to third parties. 

When you leave a comment on a post, you will not be contacted without permission and your information will not be shared.

### THIRD PARTY ADVERTISEMENTS

Third party advertisements are also used on Homedesignlover.com to support our site. 

Technologies such as cookies and web beacons may be used by some of these advertisers when their advertisements are posted or flashed on the site. This will send the advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. 

This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking and recipes sites).

### PERSONAL & CHILDREN’S INFORMATION

When leaving a comment, our comment box will require you to input your name and email address. 

All comments are subjected to approval before they are published on the post you’ve commented on. Your name, as you’ve provided it, will be publicly visible only – not your email address. 

Homedesignlover will not contact you using your email address. If you wish to contact us directly, please use our ‘Contact Us’ page. 

Please do not submit sensitive personal information in your comments/ messages to us. Sensitive personal information includes but is not limited to social security number, health information and political opinions among others. 

All this information, if submitted, will be subject to our Privacy Policy.

Similarly, Homedesignlover.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16. 

If a parent or guardian believes that we have personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, please contact us immediately using our ‘Contact Us’ form. 

We will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
